As I can see, I'm still feeling lonely
I feel the pain in my head
I'm so nervous
I'm sorry
Your smile is connected
With you, with you, with you
If you love me, if you love me
I'll be able to be with you for a long time
I won't be able to feel anything
Hello
I was surprised by the fact that the world was so big that I was able to see the world that I was born in
I wonder where I should go, and wonder why I should go back to the world of the most beautiful
But I didn't get it. I was able to see the world of the world with you, with you, with you, with you, with you
Is there anyone who came from the west?
How about this?
It seems that the river and the water were saved by this island.
Everyone saved it, right?
Everyone saved it, so it's been forgotten about the world of people.
What is the point of our death?
Lady, do you know what the point of our death is?
The point of our death?
What is it?
Did you see that?
I heard that, right?
Then, what is the point of our death?
The point of our death?
I forgot it!
I'm sorry! I'm looking for you right now!
What is it?
I was going to die here,
but...
Where did you go?
Oh!
What is it now?
It's like it's getting dark.
Is it getting dark?
Yes, it's getting dark.
And it might be darkness.
darkness?
The darkness is scary.
Is it?
If darkness comes out,
the light of the world will become dark.
If darkness comes out, it will become dark.
The darkness is from anyone else and the dark will become dark.
The darkness will become dark.
And when darkness comes out,
the light of the world will nowFAI think carefully.
The light of the world will nowFAI think carefully.
The fire is Shenatyeo and mad.
It looks suspicious.
かな?
Beloved!
Oh, I see.
I found the brother.
I did it at this place.
Oh, it's a pillow!
I was about to say this to you.
I wonder...
Brother, your mother?
Your mother?
Hey, where are you?
I can't see anything.
If the darkness comes out, the world will not light up, and the darkness will become dark.
Dad!
No! Where are you all?
Ui-ma? Don't worry about your legs.
Mom!
Ui-ma, are you still here?
Dad, I don't know!
I don't know!
It's all right. It's just a garden.
It's the first day of the first day.
I'll take care of it tomorrow.
Yes.
Come on, come on.
I'm glad.
You're a dark person, aren't you?
It's not a garden.
I'm so scared.
I was so scared.
Did you hear the sound of the darkness?
Is it really in the darkness?
It's really in the darkness!
If the darkness comes out, it will be much more scary.
It will become the world of the real darkness.
It will be the world of the real darkness.
The world of the real darkness...
Don't die.
I can't see anything.
I can't even see a nice body.
Dad!
Even if it's scary looking like that, we're afraid of something.
Now that he's cute,
I feel like friends with a boy like him.
You see.
Aren't you a boy like own basically?
We're all in the same club.
We feel excited.
Keep living together in the dark.
And we can't even hear you.
Dad, I came from within the darkness.
You want to get up?
It's like a real.
How about really anxiety?
I'm also listening to your mother's story.
I hear your mother's story as well.
If you're listening to your story, you can't be serious.
Well, I'm glad you're on the phone.
I see. Did you see me?
I was looking for Yiju, but I can't find her.
Hey!
I promised you that!
I can't find her.
Yeah, baby!
I told you to write a cool letter to me.
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
I wrote a 6-year-old letter.
I promised you two to write a cool 6-year-old letter.
That's right.
What's wrong with you?
You're so cool.
I promised you that!
I'll go now.
Really?
Oh, I see.
I told you that I'll go now.
That's right.
I was looking forward to it.
I forgot about it.
I want to go.
I'll go soon.
I'll go now.
I want to go, I want to go.
Are you always doing that?
If you know nothing, you'll go.
That's right.
Here you go.
Huh?
This is the first time I'm going to make a car's club house.
Oh, do I have to talk about the members club in fact?
Well, that's what I promised.
It was a mess.
Yeah, I'm conscience.
I wanted to see a baby.
The only one in the secret place can be found.
Hey, that's a dream.
Right.
I don't want to get married to anyone.
You'd better be able to share that.
Is that so?
I was wondering if it was real.
It was real.
That's why it's a romantic guy.
Yes, it was real.
That's right, Mr. Koji, you were planning to make a clubhouse in Honki, right?
If you say so, Mr. Yukidaru and Mr. Gan Sekiyoto and Mr. Yukidaru will tell us the truth.
Oh, I forgot about that!
That's right, Mr. Yaru.
Mr. Koji...
Mr. Koji, what's wrong with you?
I'm just kidding, Mr. Koji.
I'm so excited to see you.
Oh, no!
You're so lucky. You haven't done anything about it yet.
You're a tough guy, right?
Hey, you idiot!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's wrong, Doc?
You're going to pay for that pen.
What?
I'm really hungry, Doc!
What, what?!
Let's see what we got.
That's fun!
What's wrong, Doc?
Yeah, yeah.
Negative.
Okay, Doc, explain.
What are we doing earlier?
Is that anica?
A-A-A!
I thought the time machine was moving!
That's not what I meant!
I thought that was what I meant!
Very, I think the time machine is moving now.
That's right. The problem of the time machine is that the machine is moving.
Really? I did it!
It's amazing to be riding!
I did it!
I wasn't able to move properly, in other words.
I didn't really move until now.
It was the energy problem.
The energy problem?
It's like a rescue problem.
Well, that's the problem.
I put it in there.
Is it my pendant?
Well, let's change it.
I can change the power of the current pendant to the machine's energy.
After this energy,
if we can use the power of the current pendant and the power of the current pendant,
the current power of the current pendant will be released in the world.
Is the current pendant and the current power of the current pendant?
I'm not sure if the current power is enough.
There are things I have to know yet, but
the time machine's movement is close.
I don't know what it is, but I'm a detective.
This is a big news.
Please let me know about this.
Let's go!
I'm going to the store, too!
I did it!
It's great!
I don't know what to do, but it's fun.
I like it!
It's fun!
What is it?
I'm going to return to the world again!
I can't do this anymore!
I don't know what to do with the world, but I do.
I was so busy that I couldn't sleep!
Of course!
We're going to go to the beach!
Uiba, are you worried about that?
About that?
It's a hobby.
Yeah, I've been thinking about this for a while,
but I don't know how to do it.
I was worried too.
It's not like we've been here since we were young,
but we can't go home to find a hobby.
I know that when you come, but...
It's not like that.
You can't come back from home.
I don't want to.
We've come to the church.
And we've got something to say.
That's not right.
If you say it, you're a fool.
It's not like a shopkeeper.
It's not right.
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
I was listening to you.
I won't be able to return to the world of the Earth!
Oh, that's right!
Even if it's going to be lonely, I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you!
I know what you want to know about me, but...
Nanka-chan, if you were to return, I wouldn't have told you about the promise.
Promise?
I promised you that you would come to me someday, right?
Well, that's what I said.
I've been waiting for you for a long time since I was in love with you.
I promised you that you would come to me someday, right?
I'm sure you would come to me someday, right?
I-I'm sure, Nanka-chan, what do you mean?
That's right! I have to return to the world of the Earth, right?
I'm going to meet you!
I'm going to meet you two!
Yes!
I'm going to meet you five times!
What are you doing?
I'm going to meet you three times!
Oh, Nanka-chan!
What?
Nanka-chan!
I was waiting for you two times!
I'll be back soon!
I'm coming!
I'll be back in two and a half days!
Why not?
I'm not happy.
I'm not going to let you go!
Yeah!
You guys are stupid!
I'm going to meet you three times!
Oh, Nanka-chan!
I'll be back soon!
What?
The End
Good job!
What's wrong?
I'm a little nervous about Kyoryu-san.
Why are you crying?
It's a pity, but I'm so curious about it.
Kyoryu-san and I will call you.
That's right!
Hey, Muka Muka!
Let's call each other.
Muka Muka!
Let's meet Muka Muka!
Muka Muka?
I don't know what to do with you.
Muka Muka!
The heart of Hatsuki-chan was my problem.
I don't want to protect you.
Muka Muka!
I don't know what to do with you.
What a sad thing!
I'm so happy that you're back with Furu-san.
I can't understand your heart.
I can understand your heart!
I can't understand your heart!
Are you there?
Kupi-chan, Kupi-chan?
I'm here.
I'm sorry, Muka.
I'm sorry.
Muka Muka!
It's okay.
It's always the same as usual.
That's true.
I'm going to do my best!
Muka Muka!
Hello!
What's up, Nemuten-chan?
I'm really sorry for the delay.
What's wrong?
Hey, Rock-kun.
You're so smart, Sannan-chan.
You were just trying to claim yourself.
I hate you.
You're so smart, Sannan-chan.
It's okay, Muka Muka.
I'm going to do my best.
Why are you doing so?
Muka Muka, stop it!
You can't defeat Dota!
Me, me!
What's wrong, Muka Muka Muka?!
What the hell are you doing?
I don't like you!
I'm protecting you!
Where did you go?
I can't see you anymore.
Are you interested in me?
Kyoryu-san and Hankyo-jin-san,
the world we live in is not the only place we've ever met.
We're having fun until this end.
What is Kyoryu-ji doing?
We're really...
Hey, hey, hey!
What's wrong?
It's a little weird.
If you don't have any good plans, you can't eat!
Mom...
What?
Why don't you find me?
Did you find me?
I don't think so.
I don't know where else I should go.
And I really don't have any.
I was planning to make a fool,
but I don't think I can find you.
I just found you.
I don't think I can find you.
What?
Mom...
Are you there?
Mom, please change!
What is this?
Help me!
Mom!
Where are you?
Where are you going?
I can't find you.
Why?
This is a house!
I don't have a place to stay here.
I don't have a place to stay.
What is this?
Maybe it's a house from the other side?
It's right there!
Everyone...
Mom, I'm so sorry.
Maybe I'll be able to find you.
I'm so sorry.
It's right there!
There!
Look!
Everyone...
I'm so sorry!
It's a heart
Pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai-pai!
Shio You
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
Shio Your
It's all because of me
I'll try to get even more fun
Please subscribe to my channel!
I wonder if I can really return to the world of real life!
Next time, I'll be with Muka Muka!
I'll be with Muka Muka!